{
  "docs": [
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Kindred",
        "back": "Octavia E. Butler"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Rogue Genesis",
        "back": "Ceri London"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Shadow Over Avalon",
        "back": "C.N. Lesley"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Beholder's Eye",
        "back": "Julie E. Czerneda"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Harry Potter and the Philospoher's Stone",
        "back": "J. K. Rowling"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Interview with the Vampire",
        "back": "Anne Rice"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of To Kill a Mockingbird",
        "back": "Harper Lee"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of The Talented Mr Ripley",
        "back": "Patricia Highsmith"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of The Awakening",
        "back": "Kate Chopin"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Middlemarch",
        "back": "George Eliot"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of The Dispossessed",
        "back": "Ursula K. Le Guin"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Frankenstein",
        "back": "Mary Shelly"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Starshine",
        "back": "G.S. Jennsen"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of The Hunger Games",
        "back": "Suzanne Collins"
    },
    {
        "type": "card",
        "deck": "authors",
        "front": "Author of Dragonflight",
        "back": "Anne McCaffrey"
    }
  ]
}
